so that was really helpful because I was
able to learn things I didn't know see an
example of how it
carried out what I wanted
to do and I could go
and apply what I learned
turns out they're like extremely explosive
or reactive with oxygen they're just in
their elemental form yeah and so having
them as aluminum alloys them significantly
and they make them safer to handle
And so I think if we went
and did activities together,
I really love pickleball.
Other people in the lab probably
like playing pickleball.
Like let's go play pickleball
together, you know?
give it a baseline.
Like, here's what I'm thinking.
Is there something wrong
with what I'm thinking?
How could this be improved?
see, okay, is what it's
telling me I can do better,
actually going to make it
better, or are there problems
with what I see that it's doing?
And that'll help you think
as well while you're using
AI.